bridgewinners.com 2019-12-10

# Bridge Winners: Privacy Policy

There are many different ways you can use our services – to search for and share information, to communicate with other people, or to create new content. When you share information with us, for example by creating a Bridge Winners Account, we can make those services even better – to help you connect with people or to make sharing with others quicker and easier. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy. ** ******Our Privacy Policy explains: ** **  
****

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

Your privacy matters to Bridge Winners (Website or site), and we are committed to protecting your privacy. So whether you are new to Bridge Winners or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions [contact us.](http://www.bridgewinners.com/feedback) ** **  
****

### **General**

This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal data on our website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our site is directed to persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access this site at any time or in any manner.

We will take appropriate steps to delete any personal data of persons less than 13 years of age that has been collected on our site without verified parental consent upon learning of the existence of such personal data.

### Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users.  
We collect information in two ways:

  * **Information you give us**. 

For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a Bridge Winners Account. When you do, we’ll ask for personal information, like your first and last name, email address, and ACBL number.

  * **Information we get from your use of our services**. 

We may collect information about the Bridge Winners services that you use and how you use them, like when you create a convention card or vote on a bidding poll. This information includes:

    * **Device information** We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). Bridge Winners may associate your device identifiers with your account.
    * **Log information** When you use our services or view content provided by Bridge Winners, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs.  This may include:
      * details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.
      * Internet protocol address.
      * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
      * cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Bridge Winners account.
    * **Local storage** We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.
    * **Cookies and anonymous identifiers** We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit Bridge Winners, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifies to your device.

### How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect Bridge Winners and our users.

We may use the name you provide for your Bridge Winners profile across all of the services we offer that require a Bridge Winners Account. In addition, we may replace past names associated with your Bridge Winners Account so that you are represented in a fashion consistent to the site. We will also show other users your publicly visible Bridge Winners profile information, such as your name and photo.

When you contact Bridge Winners, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements, or to notify you when something you’re interested in has occurred on our site, like activity on a specific thread.

Personal information may be shared and disclosed as needed as part of DMCA compliance process.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

### Transparency and choice

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. For example, in your Account Settings you can:

  * Review and control certain types of information tied to your Bridge Winners Account through the Bridge Winners Profile editor
  * View and edit your e-mail notification preferences. You can also opt out of certain categories of Bridge Winners emails.

You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it’s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

### Cookies Policy

**1.        Introduction**

Our website uses cookies.

By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

**2.        About cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

Cookies can be used by web servers to identify and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and identify users returning to a website.

**3.        Our cookies**

We use both session and persistent cookies on our website.

We use cookies to allow a user to remain logged in and to personalize the website for each user.

**4.        Analytics cookies**

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website.

Our analytics service provider generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies.

The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website.

Our analytics service provider's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

**5.        Third party cookies**

Our website also uses third party cookies.

We publish Google AdSense advertisements on our website. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the web using the DoubleClick cookie. This behavior tracking allows Google to tailor the advertisements you see on other websites to reflect your interests. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: http://www.google.com/settings/ads/. You can also opt out of the AdSense partner network cookie using those settings or using the NAI's (Network Advertising Initiative's) multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you may wish to consider using the Google browser plug-in available at: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin.

**6.        Blocking cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies; for example:

(a)    in Internet Explorer (version 11) you can block cookies using the cookie handling override settings available by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy" and then "Advanced";

(b)    in Firefox (version 47) you can block all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options", "Privacy", selecting "Use custom settings for history" from the drop-down menu, and unticking "Accept cookies from sites"; and

(c)    in Chrome (version 52), you can block all cookies by accessing the "Customize and control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Content settings", and then selecting "Block sites from setting any data" under the "Cookies" heading.

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.

**7.        Deleting cookies**

You can delete cookies already stored on your computer; for example:

(a)    in Internet Explorer (version 11), you must manually delete cookie files.

(b)    in Firefox (version 47), you can delete cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options" and "Privacy", then selecting "Use custom settings for history" from the drop-down menu, clicking "Show Cookies", and then clicking "Remove All Cookies"; and

(c)    in Chrome (version 52), you can delete all cookies by accessing the "Customise and control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Clear browsing data", and then selecting "Cookies and other site and plug-in data" before clicking "Clear browsing data".

Deleting cookies will have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.

**8.        Our details**

This website is owned and operated by Bridge Winners, Inc _,_ which is registered in the State of Florida and the registered office is at _1140 Vintner Blvd. Palm Beach Gardens, FL 33410_

You can contact us:

(a)    by post, using the postal address _1140 Vintner Blvd. Palm Beach Gardens, FL 33410._

(b)    using our website contact form; or

(d)    by email, at support@bridgewinners.com.

### Information you share

Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines, including Bridge Winners. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

### Accessing and updating your personal information

You have the right to access the personal information we hold about you. Unless an exception applies, we must allow you to see the personal information we hold about you, within a reasonable time period, for no charge. Most personal information can be accessed by logging into your account. If you wish to access information that is not accessible through the platform, or wish to obtain all personal information we hold on you, please contact support@bridgewinners.com.

You also have the right to request the correction of the personal information we hold about you. Most of your personal information can be updated through the Account Settings pages. If you require assistance please contact us.

Individual Rights in the European Economic Area: If you are a Citizen of or are located in the European Economic Area, you may seek confirmation regarding whether Bridge Winners is processing personal information about you, request access to your personal information, and ask that we correct, amend or delete your personal information. In addition, you may object to Bridge Winners processing of your personal information at any time. However doing so may impact your use of Bridge Winners products and services.

### Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Bridge Winners unless one of the following circumstances apply: ** **  
****

  * **With your consent** We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Bridge Winners when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * **For external processing** We don't share information that personally identifies you with advertisers such as your name or email. We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * **For legal reasons** We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Bridge Winners if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:
    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Bridge Winners, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

If Bridge Winners is involved in a merger, acquisition, or asset sale, then your personal information may be transferred to a third party. 

### Information security

We work hard to protect Bridge Winners and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular ** **:  
****

  * We encrypt our site and your data using SSL.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
  * We restrict access to personal information to Bridge Winners employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Bridge Winners Inc. and its affiliates, including services offered on other sites (such as our advertising services), but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include Bridge Winners services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads. ** **  
****

### Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy.  When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

### Rights

  * Rights to access and control your personal data. You have the right to access your personal information that is collected or used by Bridge Winners. We offer you settings to control and manage the personal data we have about you.
  * Right to change or correct data. You can change, update or fix your data.
  * Right to Right to restriction of processing. You have the right to obtain from us the restriction of processing where one of the following applies:
    * the accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject;
    * the processing is unlawful;
    * Bridge Winners no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by you for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims;
    * You have filed a claim to processing data, pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of Bridge Winners override yours.
  * Right to take your data. You can ask us for a copy of your personal data and can ask for a copy of personal data you provided in machine readable form.
  * Right to delete data. You can ask us to erase or delete all or some of your personal data where one of the following grounds applies:
    * the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed;
    * there is no legal ground for the processing;
    * personal data have to be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in law to which the controller is subject;
    * the personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services.
  * Right to lodge a complaint. You have a right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority of the country in which you reside.

### Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, may provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).  **  
**

.
